http://www.golfspast.com/privacy.html

800-449-4097
View Cart
Powered by Spearhead Software Labs Joomla Facebook Like Button
10% Off Today
for New Email Subscribers!
HomeContactAbout UsAuthenticityCorporateGift CertsDeals
Privacy Policy Statement
This is the web site of Golf Links to the Past, Inc.
Our postal address is
305 West Lowe, Suite 100
Fairfield, Iowa 52556
We can be reached via e-mail at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
or you can reach us by telephone at 800-449-4097
Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us and we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We want you to know how we use and protect the personal information you give us. This policy (“Privacy Policy”) sets out how we use and protect any personal information that you give us when you use this Website, or on our Toll Free telephone order line or visit our store.
We do not share any information that we collect with any other organizations.
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.
We collect information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. We also collect information when you purchase products from us.
The information we collect is used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes.
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, e-mailing us at the above address, writing to us at the above address.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.
With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them .
Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address, write to us at the above address, writing to us at the above address.
Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, transaction information.
Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address.
With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
LegendsBen HoganBobby JonesJack NicklausArnold PalmerGary PlayerTiger WoodsOther LegendsPebble BeachArtAutographed ItemsCrosby/AT&T DecantersMemorabiliaBooksGiftsPhotographyMajorsMajor ChampionsThe MastersU.S. OpenThe Open ChampionshipPGARyder CupCoursesTop 100 Course PlaquesFramed Ball Marker DisplaysArchitects/ArchitectureAugusta NationalPebble BeachPinehurstU.K. CoursesOther CoursesArt/PhotographyAutographsLegendsThe MajorsLPGAOther FramedOther UnframedAutographed BallsCapsTrading CardsPhotographyLegendsCoursesMajorsCollectible Limited EditionsAntique PhotosArtOriginal Art/PaintingsAntique PrintsContemporary PrintsCanvas PrintsOther Fine ArtCollectiblesCeramicsDecantersDivot Tools & Ball MarkersGlassMoney ClipsSilver & GoldSculpturesTournament/Course Badges, Pins, Tickets, MedalsClubs & BallsReproduction HickoriesAntique HickoriesAntique BallsAutographed BallsPlayable Reproductions BallsClub & Ball Racks/BagsClub & Ball BooksBooks & DVDsVintage Rare BooksGolf Through the AgesContemporary Limited EditionsCollectible Classic Re-IssuesRecommended New BooksSubjectsBookbinding/Clam Shell ServicesPeriodicals/ProgramsDVDsGifts$100 & Under$300 & UnderTruly ExtraordinaryGift Certificates
© 2020 Golf Links to the Past, Inc.
•
Call us at 800-449-4097
ContactAbout UsSitemapPrivacy
